Jamie Joseph Heiney

Shoe Shiner

About Me

I am a highly motivated and detail-oriented individual with experience in accounting and games development for the elderly. I have a passion for customer service and enjoy making people happy by providing excellent service. I am excited to use my skills and experience in a new role as a shoe shiner.

Skills

- Accounts Payable/Accounts Receivable (AP/AR)
- Bank & Credit Card Reconciliation
- QuickBooks (Enterprise and Online)
- Google Sheets
- Excel Cash Flow Management
- Budgeting and Financial Planning
- Excellent communication
- Simplification of complex topics

Experience

Accountant

Dec 2019 - May 2022

- Managed the bookkeeping needs of several capital funding companies
- Created chart of accounts and bank reconciliation for companies
- Organized, formatted and imported large amounts of data from different software
- Designed and implemented a loan tracking system using multiple interlinked Google Sheets
- Provided consulting services to companies

Nursing Home Game Creator

Feb 2017 - Feb 2019

- Developed interactive group games for elderly care facilities
- Grew client base to over 30 nursing homes
- Managed accounts receivable and gained experience in business and management

AP Regional Manager

Jan 2015 – Mar 2017

- Oversaw AP transactions and personnel for four nursing homes
- Negotiated with vendors for more favorable contracts
- Maintained all accounts payable reports, spreadsheets, and files
- · Acted as a liaison between corporate and nursing home accounts payable departments
- Managed emails and website domains for the corporate staff

Education

Certificate - Accounting Foundations Accounting Foundations: Bookkeeping QuickBooks Online Essential Training QuickBooks Pro Essential Training Yeshiva Toras Chaim High School

Diploma - May 2008, 3.4 GPA Dual Enrollment Florida International University Accounting Course: Accounting Coach

Contact: 305-801-7497